<regions>
        <location>
                <name>Georgia Style</name>
                <description>Somewhere in between an archaic, rural fiddle style, and the more modern blues influenced style heard on the radio, Georgia was the home of many great bands and Fiddlers.</description>
                <artists>Lowe Stokes, Clayton McMitchem, and Gid Tanner were members of a seminal Georgia band, the Skillet Lickers!</artists>
                <lat>33.989092</lat>
                <lng>-84.402036</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>Round Peak Style</name>
                <description>A driving, rythmic fiddle style. Round peak players often favor fretless banjo and strong liquor with their fiddle music.</description>
                <artists>Tommy Jarrel, Kyle Creed, and Brad Leftwich are examples, new and old of the fine Round Peak style of fiddling.</artists>
                <lat>36.521179</lat>
                <lng>-80.772039</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>Western Carolina</name>
                <description>Steeped in an Appalachian tradition that has remained tucked away in the Blue Ridge Mountains since the first irish immagrants ventured there, Wester Carolina fiddle music is rich in story and lore.</description>
                <artists>The Stewart Brothers, Doc Watson, and Clarence Ashley will all get you in the mood for some Good ol Mountain Due.</artists>
                <lat>36.230912</lat>
                <lng>-81.515033</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>West Virginia</name>
                <description>West Virginia has remained connected to its rich Scotts-Irish traditions. People young and old still play the old tunes.</description>
                <artists>The Bing Brothers, Chance Mcoy, Wilson Douglas, and Melvin Wine are all important to the West Virginia fiddle tune legacy.</artists>
                <lat>38.231451</lat>
                <lng>-80.405755</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>Missouri</name>
                <description>In the late 1800s, many families moved west to Missouri as lands were already settled in Virginia and the Carolinas. they brought their fiddling traditions with them.</description>
                <artists>A lot of hay has been made about styles of fiddling in Missouri. Charlie Walden, Gary Harrison, and others have carried this tradition forward.</artists>
                <lat>37.044466</lat>
                <lng>-92.104724</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>Eastern Kentucky</name>
                <description>For years fiddlers and folklorists have prized the old-time fiddle tunes from Kentucky. The ruggedness of Kentuckys Eastern mountains helped the music retain its stark but intricate beauty.</description>
                <artists>Luther Strong, John Salyer, Paul Smith and Bruce Greene are all tradition bearers of Kentucky fiddle music.</artists>
                <lat>37.418907</lat>
                <lng>-83.001762</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>Texas</name>
                <description>Covering a range of styles almost as big as the state itself, Texas is in no short supply of great fiddle music. From Big band swing, to every towns square dance, Texas fiddle music was often associated with dancing.</description>
                <artists>Eck Roberts, Bob Wills, Jonny Gimble, and Terry Morris are examples of some of the wonderful fiddle music from Texas.</artists>
                <lat>30.721184</lat>
                <lng>-97.841086</lng>
        </location>
        <location>
                <name>New England</name>
                <description>Yankee fiddling is one of America’s most distinct musical traditions, differing from that of other regions in style, types of tunes, and general musical approach. This lively style retains much of its celtic past while blending in the frontier sensibility of North America.</description>
                <artists> Frank Ferrel, Earl Mitton, and Don Messer,  and others exemplify the Down East, or Boston Style of fiddle playing common to the region.</artists>
                <lat>43.131964</lat>
                <lng>-71.368187</lng>
        </location>
</regions>
